<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shuyang&#39;s VCD7 Docs</title>
    <description>Shuyang&#39;s blog for VCD7: Interaction Design, built with &lt;3 using Jekyll and served thru GitHub Pages.
</description>
    <link>http://shuyang.li/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://shuyang.li/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>First post!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m super excited to take the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www3.nd.edu/~amurniek/2014fa/desn31140-fa14.html&quot;&gt;VCD7: Interaction Design&lt;/a&gt; class! Last Wednesday (August 27) was our first class, and we did a quick experiment on how to mirror an iPad to the screens in the computer lab in West Lake Hall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The controls are AWFUL!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://shuyang.li/assets/west-lake-controls.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mirroring Controls&quot; /&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;small mid-gray&quot;&gt;Mirroring Controls&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, they’re not the worst I’ve seen, but in general these projection controls are difficult to work with. There’re usually a million buttons all over the place, and no one ever uses all of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this specific box, there are some tricks, as usual:
* You need to know if you’re using VGA or HDMI, and I assume not many people even know they are different;
* You have to press “Join Rooms” before choosing the source, or things will break;
* The volume knob is very gentle, and you have to roll it very far to make the volume up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So for this exercise, we made a quick movie with AfterEffects to show how the process works:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;//www.youtube.com/embed/VZrCzYooNuo?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;small center mid-gray&quot;&gt;Mirroring Process Video&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is such a painful process, but hopefully after this course I can fix it, as well as other bad user interfaces!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 10:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://shuyang.li/general/2014/09/01/first-post/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://shuyang.li/general/2014/09/01/first-post/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
